A Guide to the Linda Kiisk Architectural Collection, 1978-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Linda Kiisk Architectural Collection, 1978-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2015-054
17 Cubic Feet 8 archival boxes, six long rectangular boxes, three map case drawers
Linda Kiisk is an artist, architect, and educator specializing in sustainable design and historic preservation. This collection documents her personal and professional activities between 1968-2013, including her architectural studies, organizational activities, travel, projects, and career with her practice, Studio EESTI.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Linda Kiisk papers were donated to Special Collections in 2015, with additions in 2017.
Biographical Note
Born to an Estonian father and a German mother in northern Virginia, Linda Kiisk (1950-present) is an artist, architect, and educator specializing in sustainable design and historic preservation. Kiisk earned a Bachelor of Fine Arts in Painting & Sculpture from the College of William and Mary in 1979 and a Master of Architecture from the University of Pennsylvania in 1982. After graduation, she served as an architectural consultant for several firms in Pennsylvania, including Robert Couch, John Milner Associates, and Lymen Perry. In 1988, she began teaching at Mount Vernon College and led the Summer Study Abroad Program in Finland. In 1991, Kiisk founded Studio EESTI (Environmental Evolution Studio and Teaching Institute) to specialize in designs that teach and practice architecture. In 1994, Kiisk joined Colorado State University as a construction management professor. She cofounded CSU's Institute of the Built Environment, a multidisciplinary sustainable design and construction initiative serving public and private American institutions. Additionally, Kiisk joined the University of Wyoming in 2000 as an architectural engineering professor and studied the design and construction techniques of the Kuna Indians as a Fulbright scholar in Panama in 2004.
Kiisk has served as a member to several professional associations, including the American Institute of Architects (AIA), Women in Architecture (WIA), Union Internationale Des Femmes Architectes (UIFA), and the National Architectural Accrediting Board. Kiisk published "20 on 20/20 Vision" as a collection on papers on diversity in design in 2003 and "When Shadows Vanish" as a self-help manual in how educators, students, and professionals see the world. She served as an architect for the Wyoming State Historic Preservation Office in 2016. In her own words, this collection contains the "inside story of being a first-generation American, single parent, architect, and professor."
Scope and Content
This collection documents the activities of Linda Kiisk (1968-2012). It contains personal materials from childhood through retirement, including student work and biographical information. This collection also contains materials documenting Kiisk's career as an educator, researcher, and architect by representing business records, architectural drawings, design sketches, correspondences, clippings, photographs, and material catalogs related to several professional projects. Her major projects include Colorado State University's Institute for the Built Environment, "20 on 20/20 Vision", and "When Shadows Vanish." In addition, class lecture notes, conference information, promotional materials, home models, and course assignments are included. Furthermore, the collection includes offices records such as correspondences and financial records.
Arrangement
Arrangement of these materials reflects the Standard Series for Architecture and Landscape Design Records (Shepherd and Lowell). The intellectual structure reflects the following series and subseries:
Personal Papers
Biographical Information
Diaries
Student Work
Travel
Photographs
Professional Papers
Correspondence
Writings
Presentations
Associations
Awards
Research Notes
Research Files
Faculty Papers
Administrative
Course Materials
Research Notes
Research Files
Student Work
Institute for the Built Environment
Minoan Project
Office Records
Correspondence
Financial Records
Project Records
Files
Photographs
Drawings
Hogue Residence
McGurk Residence
Smith Residence
Cooper House Tavern
Steigerwald Residence
Stephans Residence
Sigal Kitchen
Wientzen Residence
Godfrey Residence
Mellon Residence
Art & Artifacts
Mellon Residence
Corkboard Model
Index Terms
Subjects:
International Archive of Women in Architecture (IAWA); Women architects -- California; Women in higher education; Women-owned architectural firms
Contents List
- Personal Papers
  - Biographical Info (Box 1)
    - Studio Kiisk CV (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Linda Kiisk CV (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Portfolio - Kiisk (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - CV's Linda (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Former Employments (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - CV - Kiisk (2005) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Wyoming Binder (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - CD: CV 2005 (Box 9)
    - CD: 4 Page PPT (Green) (Box 9)
  - Diaries (Box 1)
    - May 1981 Red Notebook (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Large Red Notebook (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Favorite Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - How to Make Cards (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Articles (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - TIME 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Quotes (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Sketches (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
  - Student Work (Box 1)
    - Diplomas (Oversize) (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)
    - Modern Victoria: An Era Revisited (Oversize) (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)
    - Student Assignments (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Fireplace: Design History (1981) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - University Museum (1980) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Courtyard Garden (1981) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Written Papers (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - H.M.S. Pinafore (1981) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Awards (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Home Ec Project (1970) (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - College Admissions (1975) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - High School (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - W&M Newspaper Articles (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - President's House (1975) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Alumni Gazette (1979) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Police Department Training (1979) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Myers-Briggs (1993) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Black Binder #1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Black Binder #2 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Black Binder #3 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Black Binder #4 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Black Binder #5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Black Binder #6 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Newspaper Articles #2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The Sage of Monticello (1981) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - W&M Portfolio (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Controls (Daylight) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Early American Building TechnologEarly American Building Technology (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - MC 232 Originals (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Papermaking (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - U Penn Design (1980) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax Co. Rec. Dept. Trophy (Box 9)
    - 35 mm film box: color theory (Box 9)
    - 35 mm film box: student work interiors (Box 9)
    - CD: UW Student Health (Box 9)
  - Travel
    - Panama (2004) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Il Borro (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Fulbright (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Cosmoville (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Kanchandeep (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Rangwala Tower (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Sustainable Sites Proposal (2004) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design SPIA (2004) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Finland Summer Study (1992) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Dipoli Conference Center (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Finland Pamphlets (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Photographs
    - 35 mm film box #1 (Box 9)
    - CD: Linda Kiisk (Box 9)
    - Portfolio Renders (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Professional Papers
  - Correspondence
    - Special Collections Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Mellon Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Consulting Psychologists Press, Inc. (1993) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Associated Schools of Construction (1998) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Feng Shui (2000) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Wyoming Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - AIA Correspondences (2002) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Student Letters (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1996 Interior Design Educators Council Annual Conference (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Joyce Whidden (1997) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - The Nature Conservancy (2000) (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Arizona Exhibit 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - AIA Diversity Building Bridges (1995) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - American Architectural Foundation 2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - AIA Tennessee Conferences (2005) (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - S.O.M. Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - John Milner Associates (1985) (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Marcus Correspondence (1989) (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Bonnie Sherman (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Structural System (2005) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Writings
    - Book/Research Drafts Binder (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - CD: When Shadows Vanish (Box 9)
    - CD: When Shadows Vanish Book Chapters (Box 9)
    - CD: Seeing Book Original (Box 9)
    - CD: When Shadows Vanish PowerPoint (Box 9)
    - CD: Book (Box 9)
    - CD: Book 2008 (Box 9)
    - CD: When Shadows Vanish Book Chapters #2 (Box 9)
    - "When Shadows Vanish (2005)" #1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "When Shadows Vanish (2005)" #2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "When Shadows Vanish (2005)" #3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "When Shadows Vanish (2005)" #4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Visualization Excercise (2005) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "When Shadows Vanish" Draft (2005) #5 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "When Shadows Vanish" Draft (2005) #6 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "When Shadows Vanish" Draft (2005) #7 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "When Shadows Vanish" Proposal (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "When Shadows Vanish" Draft (2005) #8 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Book Proposal (2005) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "When Shadows Vanish" Draft (2005) #9 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "20 on 20/20" Peer Review (2003) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "20 on 20/20 Vision" (2003) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Diversity Conference 2020 Vision (2005) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "Women in Green" (2007) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - NPS 1998 "Trends" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Environmental Design Charette Workbook (1996) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Green Homes" (2008) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "Our Natural Environments" (1996) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - CSU Newspaper Clippings (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Poised for the 21st Century (1995) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Erik Asmussen, Architect (1997) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Design, Construction, and Creative Thinking (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Presentations
    - CTL Presentation 5/23/03 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Aesthetic Obligation (1980) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - CD: Red Flaw PPT (Box 9)
    - CD: UW Leed Talk (Box 9)
    - CD: Leed 08 (Box 9)
    - CD: Leed Consumer Conference 2008 (Box 9)
    - CD: Beyond Utility College of Engingeering (Box 9)
    - Ways to a New Style in Architecture (1996) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Beyond Utility (2000) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Baltic Center for North American Studies (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Kitchen/Bath Design (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Associations
    - UIFA 1991 Report (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - April 2005 Status Report to AIA (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - CD: Sustainability (Box 9)
    - "Building Bridges: Diversity Connections" (1995) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - IDEC Annual Conference Proceedings (1996) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - ABC Annual Convention (1997) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - EDRA Conference (1999) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Diversity Data Summit (2003) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Conferenece Invitations (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - NSF Proposal (2001) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - UIFA 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - NCARB (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Journal of Construction Education (1996) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - IDEC Horizons & Frontiers (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - WITI Interview (1998) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Mount Vernon Annual Report (1991) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Planning Summit (1998) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Leadership Conference (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Accent on Architecture (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Diversity AIA (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Research Submission (1998) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - "Enhancing Learning for Women" (2001) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Awards
    - Architect Certificates (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Certificates (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - President's Historic Preservation Awards (1988) (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - World Trade Center Competition (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Research Notes
    - Mixed Media Floorplans (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Reference Files
    - Thinking Profile (2002) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Papers on Women (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Drawing Toward Building" (1986) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - CD: Guide Story (Box 9)
    - CD: Rapid Prototype (Box 9)
    - "Life Without A Wife" (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Fort Collins Coloradoan (1998) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Gender Based Research (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Old House Plans (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Trends (1998) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Whitewash" etc. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Interior Design Research (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Professional Development (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Grant Writing (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Feng Shui (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Women in Architecture (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Strawbale (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Landscape Architecture (2005) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Lighting References (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Floral Sketches (2010) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Lighting References #2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Design (1997-2001) (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Women Research (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Research Papers (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Architecture, Women, and Psychology (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Spatial Visualization (2003) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Women Research #2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Women vs. Men (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Seeing the Unseen (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Ecological Psychology (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Publishing Instructions (2005) (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Template Schedule (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Birgit Wolfe 99-00 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lighting References #3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Profiles (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Ortsregister (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - October 1991 "Architecture" (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Baubiologie (1998) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Ceramics (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Faculty Papers
  - Administrative
    - Teaching Evaluations (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Women's Studies Mentor (1995) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Cal Berkeley Application (2005) (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Colorado State University Interview (1994) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Recommendation Letters (1998) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - University Job Search (2004) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Course Materials
    - Alternative Building Materials (1999) (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - VHS: Lectures 2000 (Box 9)
    - CSU Industrial Science 97-98 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - ARCH History II (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Teaching Guides - New Course (1997) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Research Notes
    - Drawing Style Research (1999) (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Drawing Style Research #2 (1999) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Research Studies 1/3 (1999) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Research Studies 2/3 (1999) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Research Studies 3/3 (1999) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Reference Files
    - Recognition Papers (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Colorado State University: Color Class (1993) 1/2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Colorado State University: Color Class (1993) 2/2 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Student Work
    - INDE 62 Fall 2013 (Oversize) (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)
    - VHS: IS 232 Student Presentations Fall 1995 (Box 9)
    - VHS: Senior Design Fall 2001 (Box 9)
    - VHS: Design Projects Fall 2001 (Box 9)
    - VHS: Feb '97 - EK 330 + IS 232 (Box 9)
    - CD: Portfolio 104 PPT (Box 9)
    - Alternative Building Systems (1999) (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Undergraduate Research Symposium (1997) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Institute for the Built Environment
    - Maho Bay 1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - CSU Institute for the Built Environment (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - VHS: Presidio Case Study (Box 9)
    - CD: NPRS Presidio Case Study (Box 9)
    - CD: NPS Case Study #3 (Box 9)
  - Minoan Project
    - Minoan Project: NSF Comment Report (2002) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Minoan Project: NSF Proposal (2002) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Minoan Project: Human Subjects (2002) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Minoan Project: Human Sources (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Office Records
  - Correspondence
    - Business Documents (2000) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Client Agreements (1992) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records
    - NPS Distance Learning Budget (1998) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - CSU Expenses (1998-2002) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - O/C Builders (1988) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Madden Invoices (1989) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - McLaughlin Invoice (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Tingmalm Invoice (1989) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Maze Invoice (1990) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Hadad Invoice (1991) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Jim Ahern & Meredith Invoice (2005) (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Project Records
  - Files
    - Facilities Excellence Plan (2007) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Technical Advisory Board: Project Manual (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Lyman Perry Architects (1983) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Alliance Medical Center (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Laramie Plains Civic Center (2009) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco Fire Credit Union (2012) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Belle Haven on the Green (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Hybrid Strawbale House (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Ellbogen Center for Teaching and Learning (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Architecture Plus Proposal (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - James Marston 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Treasury Department Consultation (1989) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Whippoorwill (1992) (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Prexy's Pasture (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Weinert Construction (2010) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Crestview Meadows (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Traces (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)
  - Photographs
    - Concept Energetique System (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Laramie Rivers Construction District (2005) (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Boyd Smart (1997) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Drawings
    - EcoSmart Healthy Properties (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Meklit Fikre (1992) (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Albany County Public Library (2003) (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Laramie Cultural Center (2002) (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - A Place of Learning (2003) (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Jane Glader Residence (1995) (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Environmental Learning Center (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Woodward & Lothrop Site (1981) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Renfrew Center (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bagwell Oil (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - John Shirley (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Marju Soobert (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Mount Vernon College (1991) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Flagg Residences (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Country Club Grove (1991) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Pelster (1993) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Spangler Residence (1993) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Machanic Residence (1993) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Schmitt Residence (1994) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Czech Design (1995) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Jill Herndon Residence (1992) (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Crossway Community (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - River Song Waldorf School (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Jenny McGraw (1998) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Maija Budow (2001-2002) (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Bob Edstrom (1995) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Sreb Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - 318 Jefferson Drive (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Lay Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Thachers Lane (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Mohr Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - 5460 31st Street, NW (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Christ Church (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Dan Wangnild (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Furness Trace (Box 10)
    - 2402 Douglas Drive (Box 11)
    - Wyoming Territorial Park Addition (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - Lee Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - 7831 Winston Court (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - Arthur Ross Gallery (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - Reading Company Offices (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - View West (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - Human Brain Board (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - Lighting Contrasts Board (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
    - Building Lighting Board (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
  - Hogue Residence
    - Hogue Residence (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hogue Sketches (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hogue Residence #2 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hogue Property (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Steve Hogue Residence (Box 12)
    - Fred Hogue Property (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
  - McGurk Residence
    - McGurk Residence (2003-2004) (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - McGurk 2003 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Jim McGurk Topo Survey (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
  - Smith Residence
    - Smith Residence (2004) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Smith Residence #2 (2004) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Smith Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
  - Cooper House Tavern
    - Personal Choices (1986) (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Cooper House Resortation (1982) (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Benjamin Cooper House (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Cooper House Tavern Frame (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)
  - Steigerwald Residence
    - Steigerwald Residence (1994) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Steigerwald Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
  - Stephans Residence
    - Stephans Residence (Map-case 39, Map-case 1)
    - Stephans Residence #2 (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
  - Sigal Kitchen
    - Sigal Kitchen (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Sigal Kitchen #2 (Map-case 39, Map-case 2)
  - Wientzen Residence
    - Wientzen Residence (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Wientzen Residence #2 (Box 13)
  - Godfrey Residence
    - Katie Godfrey (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Godfrey & Lane Residence (Box 14)
  - Mellon Residence
    - West Coast Engineers (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Art & Artifacts
  - Mellon Residence
    - Mellon Residence Model (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)
  - Corkboard Model (Map-case 39, Map-case 3)